http://www.palladiumequity.com/privacy-policy/

Effective Date: December 9th, 2015
Welcome to www.palladiumequity.com. Palladium Equity Partners, LLC (along with its affiliates, “Palladium”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy helps you understand whether and how Palladium collects information about you when you visit the Site. This Privacy Policy does not address Palladium’s privacy practices concerning any information Palladium collects from its investors/limited partners; Palladium addresses those practices in separate notices sent to such persons.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as your visit to the Site is subject to it as well as the Terms of Use [insert link here]. By accessing the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy for any reason, please do not use this Site.
Palladium reserves the right to revise the Privacy Policy at any time, which will be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy will mean that you accept such amendments.
1. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY PALLADIUM. Palladium does not collect any personally identifiable information from its website visitors. Palladium also does not track other information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the websites you visit immediately before and after you visit the Site, the length of time spent on the Site or the pages accessed while visiting the Site. The only information that Palladium collects is that which is voluntarily submitted by users, for example via e-mail. By voluntarily submitting information to Palladium via the Site, you agree that Palladium may use and retain it without restriction or compensation to you.
2. COOKIES. Cookies are small text files that are stored in your computer’s memory and hard drive when you visit certain websites. This Site does not use cookies.
3. DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS. Palladium does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track signals.
4. SECURITY. The security of your information is important to Palladium. You should be aware, however, that perfect security does not exist on the Internet, and there is always the risk that unauthorized persons may access or use your information. Palladium will not be responsible for losses of your information if you use the Site to send information to Palladium.
5. CHILDREN. This Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and Palladium does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Palladium learns that a child under the age of 13 has provided it with personally identifiable information, Palladium will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from its database, subject to this Privacy Policy and applicable law.
6. APPLICABLE LAW AND JURISDICTION. The laws of the State of New York will govern this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to the jurisdiction of the federal and state courts in New York for the purpose of resolving any dispute in connection with your visit to the Site.
7. INTERNATIONAL USE. Palladium makes no representations or warranties that the Site is lawful for use or access outside the United States. If you access the Site from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are solely responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.
8. CONTACTING US. If you have any questions or comments about the Privacy Policy, you can e-mail us at palladium@palladiumequity.com or write to us at Palladium Equity Partners, Rockefeller Center, 1270 Avenue of the Americas, 31st Floor, New York, NY 10020.
Our Office
Palladium Equity Partners
Rockefeller Center
1270 Avenue of the Americas
31st Floor
New York, NY 10020
T 212.218.5150
F 212.218.5155
